<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 23:10:36 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My All Time Favorite Bullet Journal Spreads</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/all_time_fav_spreads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 23:10:36 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/all_time_fav_spreads/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I absolutely love when I have the time to really put effort into a page. It’s the perfect opportunity to use my fancy pens and stickers. Usually, I’ll practice the design on another page first to make sure everything looks just right. Here’s a collection of my favorite pages that I’ve created so far.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;scotland-trip-page&#34;&gt;Scotland Trip Page&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I was preparing for my trip to Scotland, I wanted to create a page to commemorate the adventure. I free-handed the outline of the country in pencil, including many of the small islands that surround it, and then went over it with pen. On the right side, I listed the cities we were visiting and some food/entertainment suggestions. On the left side, I added our trip itinerary. This page is one of my favorites so far—I love how it turned out!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My All Time Favorite Bullet Journal Spreads Part 2</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/fav_spreads_pt_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 23:10:36 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/fav_spreads_pt_2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m back with more of my favorite spreads from the past year! With the new year fast approaching, I’ve been reflecting on the past year, and part of that reflection has been looking through the pages of my journal. Here are some of my standout pages that I’m especially proud of. I hope they inspire you as you plan for your own journaling in the upcoming year!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;monthly-spreads&#34;&gt;Monthly Spreads&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have a few monthly spreads this year that turned out particularly well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Bullet Journal Layouts to get Things Done</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/best_bullet_layouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 10:10:36 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/best_bullet_layouts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Trust me, I’ve been there. Scrolling through endless &amp;ldquo;Top 10&amp;rdquo; lists for bullet journal layouts because you&amp;rsquo;re either not satisfied with your current setup or you’re looking for something fresh. Personally, I believe a layout should be tailored to how you want to organize your life. But sometimes, seeing a few examples or getting some inspiration can help you find the perfect style. So, here are my favorite layouts that I’ve used so far.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Bullet Journal?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/why_bullet_journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:10:36 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/why_bullet_journal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You may be wondering about the trend of bullet journaling and whether it&amp;rsquo;s something worth trying. Well, I can tell you that it has transformed my life for the better. And the best part? You don’t need to spend hours perfecting every page (despite what you might see online). Let me share my journey and offer some inspiration to help you start your own bullet journal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I first started journaling back in middle school with the small planners we were given at the beginning of each school year. I loved these planners because they helped me stay organized with all my due dates for homework and projects. I never missed a deadline! I think this is where my love for planning and making lists truly began.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
